she's someone who doesn't let politeness get in the way of progress she's gonna
say what needs to be said in any room you know what's funny is that you as a
man what your problem is is that you really should just be embracing and
welcoming to this to the fact that women are saying hey we don't like this not
arguing why we shouldn't if we say we don't like it and we are demonstrating
that then you should actually as a man who has a man who is a man of honor and
wrote a book about this should be saying well let's discuss how we can make you
all feel more comfortable and how I as a man who says that I have class
need to help and talk to my my brothers about this I don't know how we're even
kind of defending R. Kelly because the facts is he's trash
we're not butting heads and I think it's very very important especially at a
table of diverse women to very clearly delineate the
difference between having a difference in opinion than butting heads you don't
know when I'm butting heads yeah because when I butt heads there's only going to be
one head standing and I'm receiving that treatment and I know it's wrong does it
make my experience of it less it doesn't make it no so that's what we're here to
talk about my experience yes my experience is that I experienced that and it
was difficult so that's the valid part of this I'm not here to protect those
people because it's irrelevant what am I talking I just said I believe in this
country yes you can say that in a way that I cannot because you've had a
different experience because this country is here for you this country ain't here
for me in the same way sis it isn't and you as a trans person have to also
identify the fact that this country hasn't been here for trans until like
maybe two o'clock today y'all keep trying to come up with ways to undermine the
validity of my voice and I'm really tired of it I was born in America my
mother is from Grenada my father is from Boston I am the descendant of shadow
slavery in the West Indies and in America I don't need to keep explaining this
but I'm gonna do it this one last time because I'm really fucking tired of it
I'm also a fucking genius so there's a couple different reasons here why I
should be listened to one because I'm smart like a motherfucker now anybody who's
got something to say to me about otherwise can go suck a bag of dicks
when you hear men who are really ardently like you know stop empowering these
women you know women need to know that like they need to stay in a place it's
like what do you know what you're saying and I think honestly what they don't
really realize that they're saying is that we're weak yeah we're only strong if
you're not as strong as us I mean there's always gonna be a smattering of the
you don't even know what you're talking about but I do know what I'm talking
about so like what are we talking about